Register of the Daniel Lerner collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Handbooks, Guides, and Manuals, 1942-1946 (Boxes 15-27)
  - Italy (Box 19)
    - Labor, Department of Money and banking. (Folder 19: 7)
    - Office of Strategic Services
      - Communications (Folder 19: 8)
      - Education (Folder 19: 9)
      - Geographic and social background (Folder 19: 10)
      - Government and administration (Folder 19: 11)
      - Industry and commerce (Folder 19: 12)
      - Legal affairs (Folder 19: 13)
      - Natural resources (Folder 19: 14)
      - Public health and sanitation (Folder 19: 15)
      - Public safety (Folder 19: 16)
      - Public welfare (Box-folder 20: 1)
      - Public works and utilities (Folder 20: 2)
      - Transportation systems (Folder 20: 3)
    - Office of Surgeon General.
      See HANDBOOKS, GUIDES, AND MANUALS/Italy/Office of Strategic Services/ Public health and sanitation
  - Japan
    - Coal production, Administration of.
      See HANDBOOKS, GUIDES, AND MANUALS/Japan/ Foreign Economic Administration
    - Foreign Economic Administration - Administration of coal production (Box-folder 20: 4)
    - Office of Strategic Services - Population and migration (Box-folder 20: 5)
    - Population and migration.
      See HANDBOOKS, GUIDES, AND MANUALS/Japan/Office of Strategic Services
  - Military Intelligence Research Services (Great Britain)
    - Organisation Todt (Folder 20: 6)
    - SA (Sturmabteilung) der NSDAP (Folder 20: 7)
  - Ministry of Economic Warfare and Foreign Office
    - Austria
      - General
        - Part 1 (Folder 20: 8)
        - Part 2 (Folder 20: 9)
        - Part 3 (Box 21)
          - Economic survey (Folder 21: 1)
          - Local directory (Folder 21: 2)
        - Part 4 (Folder 21: 3)
      - Administration and public services under German control (Folder 21: 4)
      - German control.
        See HANDBOOKS, GUIDES, AND MANUALS/Ministry of Economic Warfare and Foreign Office/Austria/ Administration and public services under German control
    - Belgium
      - Basic handbook (Folder 21: 5)
      - Zone handbooks
        - No. 1 (East and West Flanders) (Folder 21: 6)
        - No. 2 (Antwerp and Limburg) (Folder 21: 7)
        - No. 3 (Brabant and Hainaut) (Folder 21: 8)
        - No. 4 (Liège, Luxemburg, Namur) (Folder 21: 9)
    - Germany (Folder 21: 10)
    - Germany (Box-folder 22: 1)
    - Italy
      - Basic handbook (Folder 22: 2)
      - Zone handbooks
        - Unnumbered (Sicily) (Folder 22: 3)
        - No. 4 (Lucania) (Folder 22: 4)
        - No. 5 (Apulia) (Box-folder 22: 5)
        - No. 6 (Campania) (Box-folder 22: 6)
        - No. 7 (Abruzzi and Molise) (Box-folder 22: 7)
        - No. 8 (Lazio) (Box-folder 22: 8)
        - No. 9 (Tuscany) (Folder 23: 1)
        - No. 10 (Marche, Umbria) (Folder 23: 2)
        - No. 11 (Liguria) (Folder 23: 3)
        - No. 12 (Emilia) (Folder 23: 4)
        - No. 13 (Venezia Euganea) (Folder 23: 5)
        - No. 14 (Venezia Tridentina) (Folder 23: 6)
        - No. 15 (Venezia Giulia E Zara) (Folder 23: 7)
        - No. 16 (Piedmont) (Box-folder 24: 1)
        - No. 17 (Lombardy) (Folder 24: 2)
    - Luxemburg. (Folder 24: 3)
      See also HANDBOOKS, GUIDES, AND MANUALS/Ministry of Economic Warfare and Foreign Office/Belgium/Zone handbooks/No. 4
    - Netherlands
      - Basic handbooks (Folder 24: 4)
      - Gazetteer (Folder 24: 5)
      - Zone handbooks
        - No. 1 (Lumburg, Noord Brabant, and Zeeland) (Folder 24: 6)
        - No. 2 (Zuid Holland, Noord Holland, and Utrecht) (Folder 24: 7)
        - No. 3 (Geiderland, Overijssel, Drenthe, Groningen, and Friesland) (Box-folder 25: 1)
    - Norway
      - Basic handbooks (Folder 25: 2-3)
      - Zone handbooks (Folder 25: 4)
  - Netherlands - General Services Geographic Section (Folder 25: 5)
  - Supreme Headquarters Allied Expeditionary Forces
    - Germany, Allied military government in
      - Handbook (Folder 25: 6)
      - Technical manual (Folder 25: 7)
    - Norway (Box-folder 26: 1)
  - Treasury Department - Governmental finance
    - Germany (Folder 26: 2)
    - Italy (Folder 26: 3)
  - War Department and its subagencies
    - Field Protection of Objects of Art and Archives (Folder 26: 4)
    - Germany
      - Civil affairs
        - Legal affairs (Folder 26: 5)
        - Public health and sanitation (Folder 26: 6)
        - Public safety (Folder 26: 7)
        - Public works and utilities
          - Electric power (Folder 26: 8)
          - Gas (Folder 26: 9)
        - Information control media, Employment of Germans in.
          See HANDBOOKS, GUIDES, AND MANUALS/War Department and its subagencies/ White, Grey, and Black List for Information Control Purposes
        - Wehrmacht (Folder 26; 10)
        - White, Grey, and Black List for Information Control Purposes (Folder 26: 11)
        - Japan (Folder 26: 12)
  - War Office (Box 27)
    - Denmark.
      See HANDBOOKS, GUIDES, AND MANUALS/War Office/ Notes on G.S.G.S. Maps of Germany, Denmark, and Central Europe
    - Gazetteers
      - Austria (Folder 27: 1)
      - Belgium.
        See HANDBOOKS, GUIDES, AND MANUALS/War Office/Gazetteers/France, Belgium, Luxemburg, and Holland
      - Denmark (Folder 27: 2)
      - France, Belgium, Luxemburg, and Holland (Folder 27: 3)
      - Germany
        - East (Folder 27: 4)
        - West (Folder 27: 5)
      - Luxemburg.
        See HANDBOOKS, GUIDES, AND MANUALS/Office/Gazetteers/ France, Belgium, Luxemburg, and Holland
      - Netherlands.
        See HANDBOOKS, GUIDES, AND MANUALS/War Office/Gazetteers/ France, Belgium, Luxemburg, and Holland
    - Germany.
      See HANDBOOKS, GUIDES, AND MANUALS/War Office/ Military Headquarters and Installations in Germany; and HANDBOOKS, GUIDES, AND MANUALS/ War Office/ Notes on G.S.G.S. Maps of Germany, Denmark, and Central Europe
    - Military Headquarters and Installations in Germany (Folder 27: 6)
    - Notes on G.S.G.S. Maps of Germany, Denmark, and Central Europe (Folder 27: 7)
- Intelligence Reports, 1944-1948 (Boxes 28-50)
  Daily, weekly, and monthly serials produced by various agencies of American and British governments. Arranged alphabetically by issuing agency
  - General
    - Accession list of books regarding Germany and World War II,., 1939-1945 (Folder 28: 1)
    - Intelligence bulletins,., 1945-1946 (Folder 28: 2)
    - Military intelligence reports,., June-December 1945 (Folder 28: 3)
    - Reports, October-December 1944 (Folder 28: 4)
  - Allied Commission Headquarters
    - Captured Enemy Materials Branch - Monthly Report,., 1945-1946 (Folder 28: 5)
    - Displaced Persons and Repatriation Subcommission - Monthly Report,., 1945-1946 (Folder 28: 6)
    - Economic Section. Venezia Giulia. Udine Operations Branch - Monthly Report,., May 1946 (Folder 28: 7)
    - Educational Subcommission
      - Monthly Report,., 1945-1946 (Folder 28: 8)
      - Reports,., 1946 (Folder 28: 9)
    - Finance Subcommission - Report of the Finance Subcommission,., 1945-1946 (Folder 28: 10)
    - Food and Agriculture Branch - Monthly Report,., March-April 1946 (Folder 28: 11)
    - Food and Agriculture Subcommission - Monthly Report,., 1945-1946 (Folder 28: 12)
    - Food Subcommission - Monthly Reports,., July-October 1945 (Folder 28: 13)
    - Industry and Utilities Subcommission - Monthly Report,., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 29: 1)
    - Land Forces Subcommission - Report,., 1945-1946 (Folder 29: 2)
    - Program Coordinating Branch - Report,., December 1945 (Folder 29: 3)
    - Public Health Subcommission - Monthly Report,., 1945-1946 (Folder 29: 4)
    - Public Safety Subcommission - Monthly Report,., 1945-1946 (Folder 29: 5)
    - Public Works and Utilities Subcommission - Monthly Report,., 1945-1946 (Folder 29: 6)
  - Allied Commission Headquarters - Monthly Report
    - ., 1944 (Folder 29: 7)
    - ., 1945
      - ., January-September (Folder 29: 8)
      - ., October-December (Folder 29: 9)
    - ., 1946 (Folder 29: 10)
  - Allied Control Commission. Allied Anti-Inflation Committee (Italy) - Report,., 1944 (Folder 29: 11)
  - Allied Expeditionary Forces. Supreme Headquarters.
    See Supreme Headquarters Allied Expeditionary Forces
  - Allied Military Government (Italy)
    - Naples commune - Monthly Report,., December 1945 (Folder 29: 12)
    - Public Relations Section - Report,., 1945-1946 (Folder 29: 13)
    - Venezia region - Report,., May-June 1945 (Folder 29: 14)
  - Combined Working Party on European Food Supplies - Report DI: Estimates of European Population at the End of 1943,., October 1944 (Folder 29: 15)
  - Control Commission for Germany (British Element)
    - General (Folder 29: 16)
    - Monthly Report No. 9 for., June 1946 (Folder 29: 17)
    - Report for the Month of., June 1946 (Folder 29: 18)
  - Control Commission for Germany (British Element). (Box 30)
    - Information Services Control Branch
      - Intelligence Summary,., 1945-1946 (Folder 30: 1)
      - Review of the Political Tendencies of the Newly-Licensed Press,., April 1946 (Folder 30: 2)
  - Control Commission for Germany (British Element). Legal Division - Reichsjagdgesetz (Folder 30: 3)
  - Control Commission (Military Section). Joint Historical Research Section - Reports on various subjects of German history,., 1918-1944 (Folder 30: 4)
  - Control Council (U.S. Group)
    - CINFO Report,., September 1945 (Folder 30: 5)
    - Information Control Intelligence Summary,., 1945
      - ., July (Folder 30: 6)
      - ., August (Folder 30: 7)
      - ., September-October (Folder 30: 8)
  - French Institute of Public Opinion.
    See INTELLIGENCE REPORTS/Office of War Information and French Institute of Public Opinion.
  - Great Britain
    - Admiralty. Naval Staff. Naval Intelligence Division - Weekly Intelligence Report,., November-December 1945 (Folder 30: 9)
    - British Broadcasting Corporation - Surveys of European Audiences,., 1944-1945 (Folder 30: 10)
    - Embassy (United States) - News of Hitler's Order and Public Health under Hitler's Rule,., April-June 1944 (Box-folder 31: 1)
    - Foreign Office. Political Intelligence Department.
      See INTELLIGENCE REPORTS/Great Britain/ Political Intelligence Department
    - Foreign Office. Research Department
      - Digest for Germany and Austria,., 1946
        - ., March (Folder 31: 2)
        - ., April (Folder 31: 3)
        - ., May (Folder 31: 4)
        - ., June (Folder 31: 5)
        - ., July (Folder 31: 6)
        - ., August (Folder 31: 7)
        - ., September (Folder 31: 8)
      - Extracts from Weekly Political Intelligence Summary,., April-May 1946 (Folder 31: 9)
      - Memoranda on Axis-Controlled Europe,., July-September 1944 (Folder 31: 10)
    - Foreign Office and Ministry of Economic Warfare - Notes of Economic Intelligence,., July-September 1944 (Folder 31: 11)
    - Ingersoll House Intelligence Section
      - Intelligence Summary: Holland,., June 1945 (Folder 31: 12)
      - Northern Region Intelligence Review
        - Denmark,., June 1945 (Folder 31: 13)
        - Norway,., June 1945 (Folder 31: 14)
    - Military Government for Germany.
      See also INTELLIGENCE REPORTS/Control Commission for Germany (British Element)
      - Fortnightly Report,., June 1946 (Folder 31: 15)
      - Intelligence Summary,., September 1945 (Folder 31: 16)
      - Monthly Report,., 1946-1947 (Folder 31: 17)
      - Reaction Report,., 1947 (Folder 31: 18)
      - Weekly Summary
        - ., 1945 (Folder 31: 19)
        - ., 1946
          - ., January-March (Folder 31: 20)
          - ., March-May (Folder 31: 21)
    - Ministry of Economic Warfare.
      See INTELLLIGENCE REPORTS/Great Britain/Foreign Office and Ministry for Economic Warfare
    - Political Intelligence Department (Box 32)
      - General (Folder 32: 1)
      - Austria: Weekly Background Notes,., October 1945 (Folder 32: 2)
      - Background Notes,., February-March 1945 (Folder 32: 3)
      - Digest for Germany and Austria,., October-November 1945 (Folder 32: 4)
      - Germany: Weekly Background Notes,., July-October 1945 (Folder 32: 5)
      - Intelligence Summary
        - Belgium,., February-June 1945 (Folder 32: 6)
        - Netherlands,., February-May 1945 (Folder 32: 7)
      - Nazis in the News,., 1943-1945 (Folder 32: 8)
      - Northern Region Intelligence Review
        - Denmark,., March-May 1945 (Folder 32: 9)
        - Norway,., May-June 1945 (Folder 32: 10)
      - The United Nations and the Future - Weekly Summary of discussion in Allied Countries,., 1944-1945 (Folder 32: 11)
      - Weekly Intelligence Summary: Italy,., February-September 1944 (Folder 32: 12)
      - Weekly Magazine Survey,., 1944-1945 (Folder 32: 13)
      - A Year Ago To-Day - Weekly Report,., 1944-1945 (Folder 32: 14)
      - Youth Protection Camps in Germany - Report,., July 1944 (Folder 32: 15)
    - Political Warfare Executive (Box 33)
      - Fortnightly Directive for B.B.C. Norwegian Bulletins,., March 1945 (Folder 33: 1)
      - German Propaganda and the Germans - Weekly Report
        - Undated (Folder 33: 2)
        - ., 1944
          - ., February (Folder 33: 3)
          - ., March (Folder 33: 4)
          - ., April (Folder 33: 5)
          - ., June (Folder 33: 6)
          - ., July (Folder 33: 7)
          - ., September (Folder 33: 8)
          - ., October (Folder 33: 9)
          - ., November (Folder 33: 10)
          - ., December (Folder 33: 11)
        - ., 1945
          - ., January (Folder 33: 12)
          - ., February (Folder 33: 13)
          - ., March (Folder 33: 14)
          - ., April (Box-folder 34: 1)
          - ., May (Folder 34: 2)
      - Intelligence Summary: Holland,., February 1945 (Folder 34: 3)
      - Nominal Roll (German enlisted men),., April 1945 (Folder 34: 4)
      - Northern Region Intelligence Review
        - Denmark,., August-November 1944 (Folder 34: 5)
        - Finland,., September 1944 (Folder 34: 6)
        - Norway,., 1944-1945 (Folder 34: 7)
      - Service Notes
        - Belgium,., 1944-1945 (Folder 34: 8)
        - Netherlands,., 1944-1945 (Folder 34: 9)
      - Weekly Directive for B.B.C.
        - Danish Services,., March 1945 (Folder 34: 10)
        - Greek Services,., 1944-1945 (Folder 34: 11)
      - Weekly Intelligence Summary: South Eastern Europe,., 1944-1945 (Folder 34: 12)
      - Weekly Political Warfare Intelligence Summary: Germany and Austria,., 1944-1945 (Folder 34: 13)
    - War Office - Miteuropa
      - ., 1945 (Folder 34: 14)
      - ., 1946
        - ., January-March (Folder 34: 15)
        - ., April-June (Folder 34: 16)
      - ., July-August (Folder 34: 17)
      - ., September (Folder 34: 18)
  - Military Intelligence Research Service, Washington - SS Personalities in German-Dominated Areas,., June 1944 (Box-folder 35: 1)
  - Office of War Information and French Institute of Public Opinions - Surveys,., March-May 1945 (Folder 35: 2)
  - Political Warfare Executive and Office of Strategic Services
    - France: Daily Intelligence Report,., September-November 1944 (Folder 35: 3)
    - Germany and Austria: Daily Intelligence Summary,., 1944-1945 (Folder 35: 4)
  - Supreme Headquarters Allied Expeditionary Forces
    - G-2 Division
      - General (Folder 35: 5)
      - Economic Intelligence Summary,., 1944-1945 (Folder 35: 6)
      - Enemy Communication and Supply Summary,., 1945
        - ., February-April (Folder 35: 7)
        - ., April-May (Folder 35: 8)
      - G-2 Report,., 1944-1945 (Box-folder 36: 1)
      - Martian Report
        - ., July (Folder 36: 2)
        - ., August (Folder 36: 3)
        - ., September (Folder 36: 4)
    - G-2 and G-5 division - List of reports (Folder 36: 5)
    - G-5 Division
      - General (Folder 36: 6)
      - G-5 Weekly Journal of Information,., 1945
        - ., March-April (Folder 36: 7)
        - ., April-June (Box-folder 37: 1)
      - Weekly Civil Affairs Summary
        - ., 1944-1945 (Folder 37: 2)
        - ., 1945 (Folder 37: 3)
    - Joint Intelligence Committee - Political Intelligence Report,., July 1945 (Folder 37: 4)
    - Mission to Denmark - Fortnightly Report,., July 1945 (Folder 37: 5)
    - Mission to Netherlands - Fortnightly Report,., December 1944 (Folder 37: 6)
    - Psychological Warfare Division
      - General (Folder 37: 7)
      - Daily Intelligence Digest,., March 1945 (Folder 37: 8)
      - French reports,., October-December 1944 (Folder 37: 9-10)
      - German Propaganda on the Counteroffensive,., January 1944 (Folder 37: 11)
      - Periodic Intelligence Digest (Folder 37: 12)
      - Weekly Consolidated Intelligence Report,., 1944-1945 (Box-folder 38: 1)
      - Weekly Intelligence Summary,., 1944-1945 (Folder 38: 2)
      - Weekly Intelligence Summary for Psychological Warfare
        - ., 1944-1945 (Folder 37: 3)
        - ., 1945 March-June (Folder 37: 4)
  - United States.
    See also INTELLIGENCE REPORTS/Office of War Information and French Institute of Public Opinion
    - Army.
      See also INTELLIGENCE REPORTS/United States/Office of Military Government for Germany
      - Airborne Army, 1st.
        See INTELLIGENCE REPORTS/United States/Army/European Theater of Operation/Berlin District Headquarters and First Airborne Army
      - Army, 3rd. G-2
        - G-2 Information Bulletin,., May 1945 (Folder 38: 5)
        - Military Government Weekly Report,., June-September 1945 (Folder 38: 6)
      - Army, 7th. G-2
        - G-2 Bulletin
          - ., 1945 (Folder 38: 7)
          - ., 1946 (Folder 38: 8)
        - G-2 Weekly Intelligence Summary
          - ., 1945
            - ., September-October (Folder 38: 9)
            - ., November (Box-folder 39: 1)
            - ., December (Folder 39: 2)
          - ., 1946
            - ., January (Folder 39: 3)
            - ., February (Folder 39: 4)
            - ., March (Folder 39: 5)
      - Army, 9th - G-2 Periodic Report (Folder 39: 6)
      - Army Group, 6th - Weekly Civil Affairs/ Military Government Summary,., February-April 1945 (Folder 39: 7)
      - Army Group, 12th
        - G-2
          - Counterintelligence Periodic Report No. 17,., May 1945 (Folder 39: 8)
          - Weekly Intelligence Summary,., May 1945 (Folder 39: 9)
        - Publicity and Psychological Warfare Detachment
          - Daily Summary of Intelligence,., 1945
            - ., January
              - ., 1-16 (Folder 39: 10)
              - ., 17-31 (Folder 39: 11)
            - ., February
              - ., 1-13 (Folder 39: 12)
              - ., 14-28 (Box-folder 40: 1)
            - ., March
              - ., 1-15 (Folder 40: 2)
              - ., 16-31 (Folder 40: 3)
            - ., April (Folder 40: 4)
            - ., May (Folder 40: 5)
          - Intelligence Report,., 1944-1945 (Folder 40: 6)
          - News Round-up
            - ., 1944
              - ., September (Folder 40: 7)
              - ., October (Folder 40: 8)
              - ., November (Box-folder 41: 1)
              - ., December (Folder 41: 2)
            - ., 1945
              - ., January (Folder 41: 3)
              - ., February (Folder 41: 4)
              - ., March (Folder 41: 5)
              - ., April (Folder 41: 6)
              - ., May (Folder 41: 7)
              - ., June (Folder 41: 8)
              - ., July (Folder 41: 9)
              - ., August (Folder 41: 10)
              - ., September (Folder 41: 11)
              - ., October (Folder 41: 12)
              - ., November (Folder 41: 13)
              - ., December (Folder 41: 14)
          - Semi-Weekly Intelligence Summary,., 1945
            - ., May (Folder 41: 15)
            - ., June (Box-folder 42: 1)
            - ., July (Folder 42: 2)
          - World Broadcast Trends,., May-July 1945 (Folder 42: 3)
      - European Theater of Operations.
        See also INTELLIGENCE REPORTS/United States/Office of Strategic Services
        - General (Folder 42: 4)
        - Berlin District
          - G-2 Weekly Summary,., July 1945 (Folder 42: 5)
          - Information Services Control Summary,., July 1945
        - Berlin District Headquarters
          - Berlin Press Review,., October-November 1945 (Folder 42: 7)
          - Berlin Radio Daily Extracts,., October-November 1945 (Folder 42: 8)
          - Weekly Political Summary,., November 1945 (Folder 42: 9)
        - Berlin District Headquarters and First Airborne Army
          - Information Services Control Summary,., October-November 1945 (Folder 42: 10)
          - Weekly Summary,., September-October 1945 (Folder 42: 11)
        - European Civil Affairs Division
          - General Intelligence Bulletin,., January-July 1945 (Folder 42: 12)
          - Special Intelligence Bulletin,., July 1945 (Folder 42: 13)
        - G-5 Division. Berlin District.
          See INTELLIGENCE REPORTS/United States/ Office of Military Government for Germany/Military Government Report
        - G-5 Division. Land Detachment Greater Hesse - Weekly Military Government Report,., 1945
          - ., July-August (Folder 42: 14)
          - ., September (Box-folder 43: 1)
        - G-5 Division - Military Government Weekly Field Report,., July-September 1945 (Folder 43: 2)
        - Information Control Division
          - Daily Intelligence Digest,., September 1945 (Folder 43: 3)
          - German Civilians' Reaction to a Program of Short Films,., July 1945 (Folder 43: 4)
          - Mid-Weekly Section Reports,., July 1945 (Folder 43: 5)
        - Information Services Branch,., July 1945 (Folder 43: 6)
        - Military Governor of Germany - Monthly Reports,., August 1945 (Folder 43: 7)
        - Mission to Belgium and Luxemburg - Monthly Report,., October 1945 (Folder 43: 8)
      - Infantry Division, 1st
        - G-2 Weekly Intelligence Summary,., 1945-1946 (Folder 43: 9)
        - G-2 Weekly Report,., September-November 1945 (Folder 43: 10)
      - Infantry Division, 79th - Weekly G-2 Periodic Report,., October 1945 (Folder 43: 11)
      - Infantry Division, 83rd - Weekly Intelligence Report,., October 1945 (Folder 43: 12)
      - Infantry Division, 90th - CI Periodic Report, September-., October 1945 (Folder 43: 13)
      - Infantry Division, 102nd - Weekly Intelligence Report,., January 1946 (Folder 43: 14)
      - Public Relations Division - Press releases,., March 1947 (Folder 43: 15)
    - Department of State - Air Bulletin,., May 1948 (Folder 43: 16)
    - Navy Department - Intelligence Report (Folder 44: 1)
    - Office of Military Government for Germany
      - General
        - Information Control Intelligence Summary,., 1945-1946 (Folder 44: 2)
        - Weekly Intelligence Report,., October-November 1946 (Folder 44: 3)
      - Berlin District
        - Berlin Special Survey
          - ., 1946
            - ., March-July (Folder 44: 4)
            - ., September-December (Folder 44: 5)
          - ., 1947 (Folder 44: 6)
        - Military Government Report
          - ., 1945
            - ., 1945-07
              - ., 5-20 (Folder 44: 7)
              - ., 21-30 (Box-folder 45: 1)
            - ., August (Folder 45: 2)
            - ., September (Folder 45: 3)
            - ., October (Folder 45: 4)
            - ., November (Folder 45: 5)
            - ., December (Folder 45: 6)
          - ., 1946 (Box 46)
            - ., January (Folder 46: 1)
            - ., February (Folder 46: 2)
            - ., March (Folder 46: 3)
            - ., April (Folder 46: 4)
            - ., May (Folder 46: 5)
            - ., June (Folder 46: 6)
        - Weekly Detachment
          - ., 1946
            - ., August-September (Folder 46: 7)
            - ., October (Folder 46: 8)
            - ., November (Folder 46: 9)
            - ., December (Folder 46: 10)
          - ., 1947 (Box-folder 47: 1)
      - Civil Administration Division - Semi-Annual German Police Personnel and Equipment Report,., June 1948 (Folder 47: 2)
      - Greater Hesse
        - Economic Division - Monthly Report,., December 1946 (Folder 47: 3)